mobihealthnews.com 2013-05-22

# Chester Street Publishing, Inc. – Privacy Policy | mobihealthnews

By visiting any of the websites owned and operated by Chester Street Publishing, Inc. (”Chester Street” or “the Company”), submitting information or using any of Chester Street’s services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers Chester Street’s treatment of personally identifiable information (”Personal Information”) that Chester Street gathers when you access any of Chester Street’s Sites and when you use Chester Street services or register for events provided by Chester Street. This Privacy Policy also covers Chester Street’s treatment of any Personal Information that Chester Street’s business partners share with Chester Street.

The types of Personal Information collected by Chester Street may include, but are not limited to: your full name; website URL; e-mail address; blog or other personal website URL; your nickname or screenname, and any other information that would allow Chester Street to identify you or contact you if needed. In addition we may ask you to provide certain other information such as general demographic information, including, but not limited to: age; gender; ZIP code; preferences; and interests. We may receive and store any information you enter on Chester Street’s Sites or provide to us in any other way. Chester Street will use the Personal Information you provide to operate the Company’s sites and deliver services, as well as for attribution purposes.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, your personal information will be used only by Chester Street. Your personal information will not be disclosed to any other third party without your consent. We share your Personal Information only with your consent or as described below:

1\. Business Transfers: Chester Street may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. If Chester Street, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Chester Street may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

2\. Chester Street may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Chester Street’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information shared with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to share your personally identifiable information as described herein.

3\. Protection of Chester Street and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with any law; enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Chester Street, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

4\. MobiHealthNews Resource Center and White Papers: MobiHealthNews (Chester Street Publishing) promotes content developed by Third Party Content providers typically in the form of “white papers” hosted in its “Resource Center”. This information is either hosted on a Chester Street Publishing website or on a Third Party content provider’s website. The third party partners provide this content through Chester Street Publishing in return for receiving the personally identifiable contact information of users who view their content. If you choose to view third party content, Chester Street Publishing may disclose your personal data to the third parties. If you do not want this information disclosed to a Content Provider, do not view the Third Party Content. The third party’s use of that personal information is governed by the partner’s privacy policy, and not by this Privacy Policy.

5\. MobiHealthNews Webinars: Chester Street Publishing and the vendors it hires for its online events will collect personally identifiable information during the registration process that may be shared with the sponsors of the webinar. Chester Street Publishing suggests webinar attendees read the sponsors’ own privacy policies and become aware of the sponsors’ own privacy practices before registering for the event.

Chester Street may choose to automatically receive and record information on its server logs from your browser including your IP address, Chester Street cookie information, and the page you request. Chester Street may uses “cookies” to collect non-personal data and information. In addition, Chester Street’s third-party partners or advertisers may also use “cookies.” Chester Street cannot control the use of cookies (or the resulting information) by Chester Street’s third-party partners or advertisers. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies, by changing the settings in your Internet browser.

Chester Street retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. When the Company makes changes to the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Chester Street Site, and such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. Your continued access or use of the website and/or the services shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of any amendments and/or modifications.

_Important:_ _While Chester Street maintains reasonable standards of security and confidentiality and stores Personal Information collected in a protected database, we cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to Chester Street over the Internet._

Please send any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy to [Joe Maillie, Publisher & Co-founder](mailto:joe.maillie@mobihealthnews.com "joe.maillie@mobihealthnews.com").

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 15, 2009.
